MACIEJŁOŚ

Technical Business Analyst with 4 years experience in project management and client facing roles. Recognized as a visionary and creative thinker with strong analytical skills and positive can-do attitude. Equipped with problem-solving, decision-making and excellent written and verbal communication skills. Experience in construction, real estate, hospitality and insurance industry. Enthusiast of advanced analytics, algorithms, software engineering and mountain hiking.



VISIT MY WEBSITE https://maciejlos.github.io/

CONTACT

Wrocław, Poland +48 661 900 780 maciejj.los@gmail.com

LINKS

https://github.com/maciejlos

https://linkedin.com/in/maciejlos



https://issuu.com/maciejlos/docs/portfolio



https://instagram.com/maciejlos/

LANGUAGES



INTERESTS

 mountaineering music

rock climbing

swimming

photography

cycling

architecture

piano

psychology

astronomy

sustainability

sport

EXPERIENCE

12/2021 - present Acturis Wrocław

Technical Business Analyst

- Acted as a Product Owner in charge of two products of two different business stakeholders.
- Led projects from scoping and product order sign-off till deployment and post go-live support.
- Elicited, analysed, specified, and validated the business needs of stakeholders
- Translated conceptual requirements into written functional specifications in a clear manner that is in-line with company standards and comprehensible to software developers/project team.
- Provided test data and supported the testing process in close collaboration with the developers and testers
- Provided production support including troubleshooting, root cause analysis and resolution including post-release analysis, reporting and monitoring.
- Facilitated weekly meetings with clients to gather feedback, document requirements and explore solutions
- Collaborated closely with developers, working together and discussing the best solutions and right approach for intricate features.
- Reviewed code, specifications and testpacks of other colleagues.
- Caught an issue during release testing of the product while replacing an absent colleague who was in charge of the project, preventing the bug from going into production.

Architect

10/2019 - 10/2021 Orbit Architects London

< Revit> < Sketch-up> <Autocad><Photoshop> <lllustrator><ln-Design>

< S Q L > < X M L > < A P I >

<Jenkins><XSLT><JIRA>

<Confluence><Testrail>

<Microsoft Office Excel>

- Led tender and construction stage projects of commercial buildings: 86 King William Street Rooftop Bar extension and office Cat. A fit out, The Pickle Factory Cat. A fitout,
- Delivered full documentation for tender and construction stage projects,
- Full coordination of project, direct contact with clients, consultants and project managers.
- · Resolved construction site issues, signing off main contractor works, reviewed and signed off subcontractors technical documentation.
- Dealt with complex existing scope.
- Created office Revit template.

Architect

09/2018 - 09/2019 TFK, Poznań < Revit> < Autocad>

• Led building permit stage for large-scale warehouse and office buildings,

- Full coordination, direct contact with clients, consultants and project managers,
- Resolving construction site issues.

Architect Assistant

11/2017 - 06/2018 Archibox, Poznań

• Delivered detailed drawings for building permit and executive project of multi-housing buildings.

07/2017 - 08/2017 Orbit Architects, London

Intern

• Delivered concept and detailed drawings of housing and multi-housing buildings,

• Delivered Tender pack drawings of Cat A. refurbishment and expansion of office building,

EDUCATION

02/2017 - 06/2018

Poznań University of Technology

Architecture, Master degree

10/2013 - 02/2017

Poznań University of Technology

Architecture, Bachelor degree

19/2010 - 06/2013

Comprehensiv School II liceum im. K. K. Baczyńskiego in Konin

math-physic-IT profile

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Archicad	SQL	
Autocad	Java (Spring)	
Revit	Java Script	
Sketchup	XML	
Photoshop	XSLT	
In Design	HTML	
MS Office	CSS	

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.